声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对： BillSky
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
等等  Hurley告诉过我
Wait, Hurley showed me.
就在这附近
It's around here somewhere.
肯定是的...在...
It's definitely... around...
-快点  Charlie  -噢  呃...
-Quckly, Charlie  -It's...  uh...
-我们快没时间了  Charlie.  -好的  好的
-It's definitely... around...  -Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
就在这了
Here it is!
我就说么
Told you.
当心  当心  炸药很不稳定
Be careful. Be careful. Dynamite is very unstable.
别像Arzt博士一样
You don't wanna end up like Dr. Arzt.
小心
Be careful.
Eko...
嘿  Eko
Hey! Eko.
听着...
Listen.
如果我们伤了他们怎么办?
What if we hurt them?
或是...或是炸坏了电脑?
Or blow up the computer?
你可以走了  Charlie
You can leave now Charlie.
John  我是Charlie
John? It's Charlie.
我们来想想办法  John
Let's work this thing out, John.
John  Eko很生气  John
John! Eko is very upset, John.
把门打开  我们谈谈
Let's just open this door, and we can talk about it.
John  你要知道Eko要把门炸开
John, you should know Eko is gonna blow open the blast door.
用什么炸开?
Blow it open with what?
用炸药  那些从古船拿来的炸药
With dynamite from the old ship in the jungle!
用原子弹才行  伙计
It would take an atom bomb, brother.
告诉他们别白费力气
Tell him not to bother.
你肯定不会被炸开?
You're sure it'll hold?
是的
Aye.
我确定
I'm sure.
6...5...
Six. Five.
4...3...2...1
Four. Three. Two. One.
你怎么记得你上次画到哪里了?
How do you even remember where you left off from?
慢慢的  慢慢的
Slowly, Des. Very, very slowly.
伙计  你真得看看Radzinksy是怎么做的
You should've seen Radzinsky do this.
他有照相机般的记忆
He had a photographic memory.
我是说  这全是他的主意
I mean, this whole baby was his idea.
恩  是的  Radzinsky
Yeah, right, Radzinsky.
Radzinsky发现了如何启动这假警报
Radzinsky figured out how to fake a lockdown
Radzinsky创造了这幅伟大的隐形地图
Radzinsky created this great invisible map.
我听了很多你搭档的传奇故事了
More and more tales about your former partner,
但是你却不告诉我
yet for some reason you never want to tell me
他到底发生了什么事
what bloody well happened to him.
看见那个褐色的痕迹了么?
See that brown stain there?
那就是Radzinsky留下的
That's Radzinsky.
在我睡觉的时候他朝自己嘴里开了一枪
He put a shotgun in his mouth when I was asleep.
这混蛋这么做了
The bitch of it was
搞得我只有108分钟来埋葬他
I only had 108 minutes to bury the poor bastard.
恩  如果你不想让我也疯掉...
Well, if you don't want me to go crazy,
下次让我去外面做任务
next time let me go out.
你想去外面么
Oh, you want to go out there
去和检疫与敌人战斗?
with the quarantine and the hostiles?
我已经两年没出去过了
I haven't been outside for two bloody years!
是的  我要去  我曾经是军人
Yes, I want to go. I was the army for...
对了  女皇的军队  是么?
Oh, right. Her Majesty's Army, correct?
告诉我  Desmond
Tell me, Desmond
为什么你要离开那个漂亮的老女人的军队?
why did you leave that nice old lady's army?
我记起来了
Oh, I remember now
你因为不服从命令而被赶出来了
You got kicked out because you couldn't follow orders.
那你为什么离开你的军队  Kelvin?
And why did you leave your army, Kelvin, huh?
因为人们都要听从我的指挥
Because men followed my orders.
但是后来  谢天谢地  我加入了达摩启动计划
But then, thank God, I joined the Dharma Initiative.
合十感谢  感谢你们  并祝你们好运
"Namaste, thank you, and good luck. "
求你了  Kelvin
Please, Kelvin.
让我出去
Let me go out.
就一次
Just once.
对不起  伙计  你呆在这
Sorry, Des. You stay here.
你来按按键
You push the button.
那是命令
That's order.
John
听着  没开玩笑  你就要被炸飞了
Look, seriously, you're about to be detonated!
如果John是对的呢?
Hey. What if John's right?
也许这只是个天大的玩笑
Maybe it's just some colossal joke.
你知道  这只是一台什么都没连着的电脑
You know, it's just some old computer connected to nothing.
也许只是一些电线...
Maybe it's just a bunch of wires that...
那是个玩笑么?
Is that a joke?
我还是出去吧
I'll see myself out.
John  最后给你一次机会
John! This is your last chance to end this.
打开门  我就原谅你
Open the door, and I will forgive you.
原谅我什么
Forgive me for what?
嘿  Eko?
Hey. Eko?
再等等
Just wait a second.
我不...我不觉得这是个好主意  Eko
I don't... I don't think it's a good idea, Eko.
我们空间太小了
We're in a very confined area.
胡说
Oh, bollocks!
Kelvin
嘿  Kelvin
Hey, Kelvin!
我做不到
I couldn't do it.
这是什么?
What is this?
这是唯一的另一条出路  伙计
This is the only other way out, partner.
自动防故障装置  把钥匙一转  一切都会结束了
Fail-safe. Just turn this key, and this all goes away.
墙后面是什么  Kelvin?
What's behind that wall, Kelvin?
恩?
Huh?
那个意外是什么?
What was the incident?
是电磁
Electromagnetism.
独特的地质现象
Geologically unique.
意外就是...电磁泄露了
The incident? It was a leak.
现在正在充电
So now the charge builds up
每次我们按按键
and every time we push the button
电力就放掉一点...
it discharges it.
这样就不会使磁力太强
Before it gets too big.
为什么要我们来...按按键?
Why make us do it? Push the button?
如果我们...如果我们...
If we can just...
这就是问题所在了  Desmond...
Now here's the real question, Desmondo
你有勇气
Do you have the courage
伸出你的手
to take your finger out of the dam
来结束这一切么?
blow the whole thing up instead?
我想你的朋友们炸伤他们自己了  伙计
I think your friends just blew themselves up, brother.
也许我们该把门打开
Maybe we should open it.
不  不
No! No.
这是个骗局
It's a trick.
一个骗局?  他们可能受伤了
A trick? They could be hurt.
你们医生在附近么?
Is your doctor around?
能问你个问题么  伙计?
Can I ask you a question, brother?
当然
Absolutely.
这是否就是你让这钟
Is the reason you're letting that clock there
走完最后一秒的原因...
run all the way down to the very last tick...
因为你需要查明真相...
Is it because you need to look down the barrel of a gun...
来找到你真正相信的东西  John?
...and find out what you really believe, John?
我之所以要查到底
I looked down the barrel of the gun.
是因为我相信
And I believed.
我以为...
I thought...
来到这里是我的命运
it was my destiny to get into this... place.
而且...有些人死了
And somebody died.
你知道  一个孩子...因为他愚蠢到相信
A kid. Because he was stupid enough to believe
我所知道的和我所说的
that I knew what I was talking about.
那晚他死得毫无意义
And on the night he died for nothing
我独自一个人呆在这上面
I was sitting right up there all alone
用我的手敲着...
beating my hand bloody against that...
该死的舱门
stupid door.
朝天大喊  问我到底应该怎么做
Screaming to the heavens, asking what should I do.
然后亮出了一道光线
And then a light went on.
我以为这是一个暗示
I thought it was a sign.
但这不是什么暗示
But it wasn't a sign.
可能只是你去了洗手间
Probably just you going to the bathroom.
Jack?
它们是什么?
What are they?
是手写的
It's handwritten.
整本书都是...
And it's all filled. The whole book.
都是些日志
They're journal entries.
0400...S.R. 再次移动了乒乓桌
0400. S.R. Moves Ping-Pong table again.
0415...淋浴
0415. Takes a shower.
这是什么?
What is this?
医生  你说过Sayid到达海滩
Hey, doc? What'd you say Sayid's sign
解决了那里的海滩派对以后会给我们发信号
was when the coast was clear to hit that beach party?
那就说明他找到他们了  是么?
That means he found them, right?
那离这里还很远
That's miles from here.
你在把我们往哪里带?
Where were you taking us?
-什么?  -Sayid说他会点起信号
-What?  -Sayid said he'd light the signal
这样我们就可以在岸边和他会合了
so we'd meet him at the shore.
-我们为什么没去海滩?  -我们就是去...
-Why aren't we going to the beach?  -We are.
-我们根本不是去海滩  -听着  我不得不...
-We're nowhere near the beach!  -I had to.
什么?
What?
Sawyer
快走  快逃  快逃
Run! Go! Go!
等等  等等
Hold on. Wait!
你找到的另一个舱子...
Tell me about this other hatch you found.
那个...珍珠
This... Pearl.
珍珠是一个监测站
The Pearl is a psychological station
摆满了监视器
full of TV monitors.
两个人坐在椅子上
two men sat in X chairs
在记事本上写观测到的
and filled notebooks with observations
这里发生的情况
on what happens in here.
然后他们把记事本放进空的容器
And then they put the notebooks in pneumatic tubes
送给他们的指挥部
that sent them to their headquarters
这样他们就能用我们来做试验了
so they could evaluate us as an experiment.
什么?
What?
-如果你反过来想一想呢?  -反过来?
-What if you've got it backwards?  -Backwards?
如果试验对象不是这里的两个人
What if the experiment wasn't on the two men here
而是那里的两个人呢?
but on the two men in there?
听着  我想看那卷录影带  John
I want to see that tape, John.
不  你在这里无法看到
No, you can't. There's no way to see it down here.
在那个站里还有别的东西么?
Was there anything else in that station?
-有电脑么?  -有的
-A computer?  -Yeah.
-那是用来干吗的?  -没用  那个电脑没什么用
-So, what did it do?  -Nothing! It didn't do anything.
它打印出数字...很多很多的数字
It printed out numbers. Lots of numbers.
What printer? Where is it?
什么数字?  在哪?
给你  剩下的19分钟好好读吧
Here. Reading material for the next 19 minutes.
省得没事干
Knock yourself out.
三年来你天天刮胡子
You've been shaving for the last three years.
你应该留着一点
You need to live a little.
让它长出来
Let go.
我不会让它长出来的  伙计
I'm never gonna let go, brother.
噢  那就是动力了
Oh, that's the spirit.
再见  伙计
Goodbye, Des.
再见?
Goodbye?
是的
Yeah.
再见
Goodbye.
几小时后见
See you in a couple hours.
真糟糕  我没想到
Well, gosh. I didn't think
你靠石头的掩护来跟踪我
you had the stones to come after me.
我已经有十年的经验了
I was a spook for ten years, Des.
当有人跟踪我时我是知道的
I know when I'm being followed.
-你拿我的船来做什么?  -我正在修
-What are you doing with my boat?  -I'm fixing it.
你要走了?
You were leaving?
恩  我是说  不是现在 还要一周左右才能修好
Well, I mean, not yet. She's still about a week away.
你把它损坏得够呛的
You wrecked her pretty good, Des.
你怎么想?  你想和我一起走么?
So, what do you think? Want to come with me?
去哪里?
Come where?
按键怎么办?
What about the button?
忘了那个按键吧  伙计 谁知道它是不是真的?
Screw the button, man. Who knows if it's even real?
你可不是这么说的
when you were going on about dams and electromagnetics and fail-safes!
我当时喝醉了
I was drunk.
你为什么要骗我?
Why did you lie to me?
我需要另一个人来拯救世界
I needed a sucker to save the world after I left.
你这个疯子  你这个混蛋
You're crazy! You bastard!
-好了  -你毁了我的生命
-Oh, come on.  -You stole my life!
你还骗了我什么?  还有呢?
What else did you lie to me about? What else?
告诉我告诉我
Tell me!
你怎么能这么对我?  起来
How could you do this to me? Get up.
天那
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
错误...系统错误
Failure. System failure.
系统错误
System failure.
拜托
Come on!
系统错误
System failure.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
你们什么时候来的?
When did you come here?
什么?
What?
这个岛
The island.
你们什么时候来的  多久前?
When did you come here? How long ago?
60到65天前吧
Sixty, 65 days.
-具体日期?  具体是什么时候?  -9月22号
-The date! What was the date?  -September 22nd.
是9月22号
It was September 22nd
我想是我让你们坠机了
I think I crashed your plane.
狗娘养的  我要踢死...
Son of a bitch, I'll kick your...
大家都静一静
Everybody just calm down!
是假的
It's fake.
我们知道你胡子是假的
We know that your beard is fake.
抱歉  小姑娘  我没听懂
Sorry, missy. I didn't get you.
她说她知道你胡子是假的  Tom
She says she knows your beard's fake, Tom.
恩  谢谢你指出  Kate
Well, thanks for pointing that out, Kate.
我得告诉你这东西真的很痒
I can't tell you how much this thing itches.
还要谢谢你告诉他们我的名字  Bea
And thanks for telling them my name, Bea.
你们好
Hello, again.
你的胡子呢?
Where's your beard?
我想...他们知道了
I think... they know...
好了  我们开始谈我们的交易吧  好么?
All right. Let's take care of business, shall we?
Eko  Eko
我是Charlie
It's Charlie.
醒醒
Wake up!
-不  我们得按按键  -不  我们不能按
-We need to push the button.  -No, we don't.
你没听我说么  伙计?  是我让你们坠机的
Did you not hear me? I crashed your plane.
你怎么做的?
How did you manage to do that?
那天  这些数字变成了象形文字
On that day, those numbers turned to hieroglyphics.
当最后一个稳定下来时
When the last one came down
整个地方就开始摇晃了  屏幕上...
this place started to shake.
屏幕上打满了"系统错误"
That screen filled up with "system failure. "
系统错误
"System failure. "
这里的数字...92204...
And that number there: 92204.
9月22号  2004年...
September the 22nd, 2004.
你们坠机的那天  是真的  都是真的
The day your plane crashed. It's real! It's all bloody real!
-现在按这该死的按键  -我知道我看到了什么
-Now push the damn button! -I know what I saw!
都是骗人的  都不是真的  全部都是假的
It's a lie! It's not real! None of it is real!
你不想按按键么?  那么我来按
You don't want to push the button? Then I will.
不
No!
你杀了我们
You've killed us.
你把我们全杀了
You've killed us all.
不
No.
我救了我们大家
I just saved us all.
Eko  醒醒
Hey! Eko! Wake up.
可以帮忙么
Hey! Can I get some help?
-可以帮帮我么  -我是在帮你  伙计
-Can you help me?  -I'm trying, brother!
亲爱的  在你离开监狱的时候
Dearest Des. I'm writing this letter to you
我写这封信给你
as you leave for prison.
我把它藏在了你在完全绝望时
And I've hidden it in the one place
会去看的地方
you would turn to in a moment of great desperation.
我知道你走
I know you go away
是因为
with the weight
你肩上的压力
of what happened on your shoulders.
而且我知道只有你自己才能甩掉压力
And I know the only person who can ever take it off is you.
别放弃  亲爱的
Please don't give up, Des.
因为我们需要赖以为生的
Because all we really need to survive
是一个真正爱我们的人
is one person who truly loves us.
现在你得到了
And you have her.
我会等你的  永远
I will wait for you always.
我爱你
I love you
Pen
都结束了
It's all gone.
都...都结束了
It's all... It's all gone.
全都结束了
All gone!
我做了任何你要求我做的事
I've done everything you wanted me to do
那么你为什么这么做?  为什么?
so why did you do this? Why?
你们下来的三天前
Three days before you came down here
在我们见面之前
before we met
我听见敲打舱门的声音  有人在大喊
I heard a banging on the hatch door, shouting.
那人就是你  John  不是么?
But it was you, John, wasn't it?
你说没什么事是注定发生的
You say there isn't any purpose?
没有命运这么一回事?
No such thing as fate?
但是你救了我  伙计 所以我要救你
But you saved my life, brother. So that I could save yours.
不不不  这些都不是真的
Don't! No! No! None of this is real!
不会发生什么事的  我们会没事的
Nothing is gonna happen! We're gonna be OK!
我必须要这么做
I've got to go
你得离这里越远越好
and you've got to get as far away from here as possible.
去哪里?  停下
Go where? Stop!
我要炸了这里  John
I'm gonna blow the dam, John.
我很抱歉有些事让你不再相信这个
I'm sorry for whatever happened that made you stop believing.
但这全是真的
But it's all real.
现在我要去结束这一切了
And now I've got to go and make it all go away.
等等  Desmond
Wait! Desmond?
在新生活中再见了  伙计
I'll see you in another life, brother.
系统错误  系统错误
System failure.
系统错误
Eko  醒醒
Eko! Eko! Wake up!
你还好吧?
You all right?
不
No.
天哪
Oh, my God!
-好了  跟我来  -Charlie...
-Come on! Come with me!  -Charlie...
-不  我不...  -离开这里 快点
-No! Hang on!  -Get out of here! Go!
John
Eko
是我错了
I was wrong.
我们需要赖以为生的
All we really need to survive
是一个真正爱我们的人
is one person who truly loves us.
现在你得到了
And you have her.
我会等你的
I will wait for you
永远
always.
我爱你
I love you.
我爱你  Penny
I love you, Penny.
Charlie?
你没事吧?
You OK?
只是...
It's
很难说清楚  但我的耳朵  你知道
It's hard to tell exactly, Bernard. My ears... You know?
-Locke和Eko呢?  -他们还没回来么?
-Where's Locke? Eko?  -They're not back yet?
没有
No.
我对你的安排
I'm not happy about the arrangement
感到非常不满意 Michael
that was made with you. Michael
但是当Walt加入我们后
but we got more than we bargained for
我们得到的比预计的多
when Walt joined us.
所以我认为那是最好的方面
So I suppose this is what's best.
并且你放了我
And you let me go. Set me free.
你遵守了诺言
You lived up to your word.
我们也遵守我们的诺言
We live up to our word too.
你知道怎么开船么?
You know how to drive a boat?
-是的  我会开  -好的  那艘船给你
-I can drive a boat.  -Good. You're gonna take this boat
顺着指南针325的方向开
and follow a compass bearing of 325.
如果你准确按照方向的话
And if you do that exactly
你和你的儿子就获救了
you and your son will find rescue.
什么  就这样了?
What, that's it?
我照着方向开  我和我儿子就获救了
I follow the bearing, and me and my son get rescued?
是的
Yes.
你怎么知道我不会告诉人们
How do you know I won't tell people
这个岛在哪里?
about where I was?
也许你会  也许你不会
Maybe you will, and maybe you won't.
但是都无关紧要
But it won't matter.
一旦你走了 你再也不可能回来了
Once you leave, you'll never be able to get back here.
并且我相信你是不会和别人说起的
And my hunch is you won't say a word to anybody.
因为一旦你说了
Because if you do
人们就会知道
people will find out
你是怎么要回你儿子的
what you did to get your son back.
我的朋友们
My friends.
你保证过不会伤害他们的
I was promised you wouldn't hurt them.
说话算话
A deal's a deal.
你们到底是谁?
Who are you people?
我们是好人  Michael
We're the good guys, Michael.
好了  它是你的了
All right. She's all yours.
什么? 我是傻子么? 我儿子呢?
What? What, am I stupid? Where is my son?
Walt就在里面
Walt's inside.
Walt?
旅途愉快  Michael
Bon voyage, Michael.
Walt
爸爸  爸爸
Dad! Dad!
过来  过来
Come here. Come here.
-你还好吧?  -是的  我很好
-You OK?  -Yeah, I'm OK.
你肯定么?
You sure?
好了  我带回你了
OK. I got you now.
现在没事了  我们回家了  Walt
It's gonna be OK, now. We're going home, Walt.
我们回家了
We are going home.
Hugo  你可以回去了
Hugo, you can go back to your camp.
什么?
What?
回去
Go back.
你的工作就是告诉你们剩下的人
Your job is to tell the rest of your people
叫他们别来这里
they can never come here.
但是...我的朋友呢?
But what about my friends?
你的朋友们和我们一起回家
Your friends are coming home with us.
走吧
Go.
发生了什么事  Charlie?
What happened out there, Charlie?
你想听
You want to hear the part
我差点被那个闪光的火球杀死
about me nearly being killed by the flaming fire ball
还是差点被那个飞来的叉子叉死?
or the flying fork?
我要你认真的说
I want you to be serious.
什么都没发生
Nothing happened.
发生了很多事情
Well, something happened.
我是说  那些声音
I mean, that noise
还有天空变成了紫罗兰色
and the sky turned that weird violet color.
真的么?
Did it?
我击垮了你的防守
你的车已经没有了
这都是计划的一部分  朋友
啊  那你的计划就是失败了
快点  该你了
怎么了?
那盏灯亮了多久了?
就是那个  对吧?   我们又错过了...
我们没错过
这次不是假警报了?
闭嘴  快去打电话
你好
Hello?
Widmore小姐么?
Ms. Widmore?
是的
Yes?
是我们
It's us.
我想我们找到了
I think we found it.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====